CURICULUM VITAE

Rosechell C. Gonzaga, RN Building 49, Zone 55, Street 762 Bu Sidra, Doha Qatar



Career Summary

A dedicated, patient – focused registered nurse with proven experience in OPD, Emergency Room, Uro-Surgery, Dermatology, Ob/Gyne, General Practitioner, Pediatric, Internal Medicine, Dental and E.N.T., and Home Care Nurse. Proficient in providing the quality assistant to a doctor. Able to work with my own initiative with the support of other health care procedure and practices are adhered to.

Objectives

Seeking a responsible and challenging position where my profound medical professional and practical experiences be fully utilized in your reputed hospital.

Personality Traits

- Strong work ethics and leadership
- Excellent in communication skills both written and verbal
- Ability to work in pressured situation
- Ability to take care of patient excellently
- Staff briefing
- Team motivation and team work
- Able to handle complains
- Performs therapeutic nursing intervention
- Efficient and responsible
- Willing to adjust duty hours

Personal Qualities

- Good initiator
- Hardworking
- Humble
- Patience
- Resilient
- Easy to adapt to change of environment
- Wilingness to learn

Professional Working Experience

Staffnurse (Al-Shefa Polyclinic/2002-2004)

IV nurse/ Charge nurse(Casaul General Hospital/1999-2002)

Staffnurse (Dammam National Medical Complex)

September 20,2005 up to September 30,2013

- Give direct nursing care and utilize the process
- Observes sign and symptoms institute remidial actions when appropriate and do the documentation
- Reports observation to the physician
- Observes and response to patients emotional and spiritual needs
- Takes and record vital signs
- Observes medical/surgical asepsis
- Carry out doctors order
- Performs ECG
- Performs intraveous infusion with care and gives injections prescribed by the doctor
- Sees to it that equipment received, endorsed with proper care and maintenace
- Acts as senior nurse when so delegated
- Interprets hospital policies and procedures
- Give health teaching
- Maintain good relationship with other health personnel

Headnurse (Dammam National Medical Complex)

September 2013 up to September 2017

- Proven ability to manage and evaluate nursing staff
- Strong written, verbal and interpersonal communication skills
- Proficiency in multi-tasking and handling stressful situations
- Talent for negotiation and collaborations
- In-charge of teams of nurses or decision of health care facilities
- Responsible for the performance of their teams meaning have to monitor the nurses who work under them and ensure they are fufilling all their job requirements
- Able to organize, compile and store all the notes on patients taken by their nursing team
- In-charge of hiring, screening potential employees, looking over resume, conducting interviews and making hiring decisions
- In-charge of training the new hired employees
- In-charge of maintaining working relationships with their staffs, which includes scheduling, pay and conflict resolution where necessary.

Assistant Headnurse/Duty nurse(Resala Care from April 2018 – March 2021) Headnurse/Duty nurse (Resala Care March 2021 up to present)

Certifications

- Best Nurse
- Basic life Support
- Immediate Life support

Seminars attended with CME hours Compassionate Human Interaction(CHI)

Living With Dimentia-Together Redefining Quality Of Life

Education

Secondary - Saint Vincent Institute

Maribojoc, Bohol

Tertiary - Dr. Carlos S. Lanting College

Bachelor of Science In Nursing

Sangandaan, Novaliches Quezon City

Philippines

Personnal Background

Sex: Female Civil Status: Married

Birthday: March 18,1977
Age: 46yrs old
Nationality: Filipino
Passport # P1321936B

Eligibility

Nursing Licensure Exam(philippines)—Passed Prometric Exam(Saudi Arabia) -- Passed Prometric Exam(Qatar)---Passed

References

Mr.Mohamad Sebbae Manager Director Resala Care

Phone #0097433318886

Mrs. Geraldine Zozobrado Nurse Director/Nurse Educator Resala Care Phone#0097433476485 Ms. Marie Alamag HR Manager Resala Care

Phone#0097466466205